##
ADAM: I was a good soldier.
I had purpose,
and I loved it.
[GUNFIRE]
I rode shotgun in a lead Humvee,
and I looked for bombs.
You don't see the bomb unless they want you to.
You sense it.
- You just know.
- [DISTANT EXPLOSIONS]
I avoided the bomb that day...
but led us right into an ambush.
[GUNFIRE]
- That's how Emory happened.
- Clear.
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[UNDER BREATH] Fuck.
[GUNSHOT ECHOING]
Man down!
Hang on, Emory. I got you.
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
[EMORY GROANING QUIETLY]
Hang on, Emory.
Hang on.
- I got you.
- [EMORY GROANS]
Hang on, buddy. Hang on.
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
[EMORY GROANING LOUDLY]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[GASPING]
- MAN: [OVER RADIO] Uh, 1-4-1-3-1-7.
- Roger that. Waiting on 1-1.
##
[LAUGHTER NEARBY]
Oh, my God. Why are fat people so funny?
I swear, the funniest fuckers
that ever lived, they're always
- they're always fat motherfuckers, you know?
- What, is that why you're getting out?
- You're gonna get fat?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I'm getting fat.
- Chappelle isn't fat.
- Then you got Chris Rock...
- Nah, nah, you're doing...
- you're doing a black thing.
- What?
- No... doing a black thing?
- You're doing a black thing.
No, I'm not, man. I'm doing...
- doing a funny thing.
- What, black don't count?
Yeah, nice try, Samo.
- You're barely black. I've seen you naked.
- Ooh. I've seen your weak shit, too, boy.
One and done, and didn't see shit.
Yeah, you've been one and done your whole life.
- This my second deployment, dumb fuck.
- Yeah, if you had any fucking brains up there,
- it'd be your fucking last.
- Fuck that. Army saved my life.
Yeah. Okay.
So, when's the bachelor party, champ?
Oh, man, I can't have a bachelor party.
You've seen me drunk.
- Yeah, you'd fuck a blister.
- So what?
Nah, nah. My girl's not into it, and...
you know, I just don't want
to fuck this up, all right?
- So much for balls, man.
- Hey, look.
The bachelor party's none of her business,
all right? That's our thing.
Look, I... I want you guys to come meet
her before the wedding, though.
Shit, th... this guy, that's all he talked
about for the past 11 months.
- I feel like I'm married to her.
- Dude, in that fucking video,
when you're going like that and...
- [LAUGHING] Oh! Ooh!
- Fuck you, man.
- You serious?
- Yeah.
If she found out you saw that, seriously...
- I just didn't know you're left-handed. That's...
- Dude...
Guys, don't fuck with me, man.
Seriously, don't fuck with me.
Hey, nobody saw shit, all right?
- That stays here.
- It's a fucking joke. Okay? OPSEC.
[CHUCKLING] It was a pretty great video, dude.
[CHEERING]
- Hey, stay off the streets, all right?
- I'm back in the sand in three months.
That's not what I said.
MAN: Private Morgan.
- PFC Waller.
- All right.
MAN: Specialist Watkins.
Thank you.
Sergeant Schumann.
Welcome home, Sergeant Schumann.
MAN: Private McGarrett.
Specialist Aieti.
[CHEERING CONTINUES]
Sergeant Schumann. I'm Amanda Doster.
I need you to tell me how my husband died.
Sergeant Doster.
James Doster.
Were you there... when he died?
- No.
- Did he suffer?
What did he say? I need to know.
Tell me how my husband died.
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom.
Can we get a pie?
Of course we can.
Eat your dinner first.
You girls look so pretty.
- [BABY COOS]
- What about Jaxy?
[BABBLES]
And Jaxy, yeah.
That's a sweet little jumper there, buddy.
[LIGHT LAUGHTER]
[JAXSON COOING]
I can't believe Amanda did that.
- She ruined everything.
- Doesn't matter.
- We wanted to make it nice for you.
- It is nice.
That was supposed to be perfect.
- We wanted it to be perfect.
- It is perfect.
I'm here. I got all my limbs. I got all
my pieces, with my favorite girls.
And Jax.
It's perfect, baby.
[TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
I want to have a baby, Sol.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY] You
can't wait till we're home?
My beautiful wife...
You are getting out, right?
They'd probably come after me to reenlist, but...
Solo.
I'm just saying.
MAN: You back from Iraq?
Yes, sir.
11 months and 19 days.
You kick some ass over there?
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
- SASKIA: Where are you going?
- I want to swing by the old house.
Are you trying to make yourself crazy?
Maybe.
How are the renters?
I'd like 'em a whole lot more if they
didn't live in our fucking house.
They're not watering my lawn.
We'd probably still live here if
you hadn't bought that pool.
- Our kids are gonna learn to swim in that pool.
- Oh, yeah?
Are they gonna learn how to swim
when they're teenagers?
Where did that come from?
We're getting back in this house.
Hello?
Tracey?
Tray.
Baby.
[UNDER BREATH] Fucking...
##
[RECORDING, OVER PHONE] This is Tracey.
Please leave a message, and I'll get back to you
- when I can.
- [BEEP]
Tracey, where are you? Where's our furniture?
I'm trying not to freak out,
but I just got back, and...
the electricity's off.
My debit card isn't working.
Can you call me?
I love you. Just... just call me, all right?
[OBJECTS RUSTLING]
[PANTING]
This is Tracey. Please leave a message,
- and I'll get back to you when I can.
- [BEEP]
Tracey, where the fuck are you?
- ADAM: How much we save by living here?
- SASKIA: Not enough.
["FADE INTO YOU" BY MAZZY STAR PLAYS]
- Am I getting laid or what?
- Oh, yeah, you're getting laid.
- In fact, I might lay an egg up in here.
- No more eggs or seeds or any of that.
Come on, you don't want another one?
Let's see how you feel after
a weekend alone with them.
And where do you think you're going?
- Hmm.
- Hmm?
You left three times.
Now it's my turn.
Well, I'm not leaving again.
I'm home for good.
# I look to you and I see nothing #
# Close your eyes... #
Do you remember who we were before all this?
- Couple dumb, horny kids.
- Pretty much.
- Still dumb and horny.
- With a couple kids.
- [DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
- # Fade #
[TRAIN HORN BLOWS IN DISTANCE]
[WHIPPING, SCRAPING]
##
[PANTING]
How long you been up?
It's already 4:00 p.m. in Baghdad.
You guys ready for some hotcakes?
Are you chewing gum?
When did you become a gum chewer?
Tell me... you didn't miss my pancakes.
Smells good.
I need you to watch the kids today.
- Can you handle them for a couple hours?
- Yeah.
Sure can.
All right.
I got some bacon here.
It's you and me today, Zo.
[CHUCKLES]
And Jax.
And the Jax-man. Got it.
I was thinking... my mom could babysit tonight,
and we could go to the speedway.
You know I like that.
Hey.
I'm gonna stop by the golf course later,
see if they need any greensmen.
Okay.
- What?
- It's a kid's job.
Same job I had before.
You were just in charge of a dozen men,
and now you're gonna mow grass?
[INDISTINCT PROGRAM PLAYING OVER PHONE]
- Hey, could you turn that off, Zo?
- No.
All right.
Got one chocolate chip smiley
face pancake for you.
I hate chocolate.
You do?
- Yes, silly bum-bum.
- Hey.
She doesn't like chocolate.
Okay. I guess I missed that part.
What else? Anything else that I missed?
Here you go, Specialist.
##
MAN: What are you taking the Somex for?
It was to sleep over there.
And what about the propranolol?
Yeah, don't think I was taking that.
Are you bothered by racing thoughts?
No, sir.
Reliving past events?
Not really.
Any lapse in memory?
- Well, I lose stuff sometimes.
- You mean you misplace things?
Yeah, or things I was gonna do
or... trying to remember if I did.
How about mood swings?
No.
When you were hit with the IED, did you
experience discharge from the ears?
I just want to get back to my unit.
The company physician at Rustamiyah
documented complaints
consistent with traumatic brain injury.
I feel good.
I'm ready to go back.
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Do you want a blow job?
- Right here?
- If it'll make you feel better.
Don't underestimate me.
I'm tougher than you are,
so you don't have to spare me the details
'cause you think I can't take it.
I can take anything you can.
Anything but quiet.
It was just different this time.
Different how?
This one felt a lot longer.
Towards the end, things took
a turn and got really bad.
Were you with Doster when he died?
No. I wasn't there.
[QUIET CHATTER, MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY]
Sometimes they go a little crazy
when we're gone, right?
- You just got to give her a minute.
- It's not like she packed a bag, dude.
She cleaned me out.
I got to figure this out, you know?
- Well, can we see that nudie video, then?
- Su... such a dog.
What, you got a video, Shoe? She's hot, man.
- I will fuck you up.
- You promise?
I swear, it's like, the whole time you're out
there, all you want to do is come home.
Come home, and home is
just fucked, you know?
- Hey, you had a rough landing, buddy.
- SOLO: Yeah, fucking crash landing.
I got to make some money.
That video, bro.
- You serious?
- I'll give you 20 bucks for it.
- You, too, Shoe?
- Yeah... 20 bucks.
Hey, maybe I'll just redeploy with you, Solo,
stack checks for nine months, you know?
Hey, I tell you what, I fucking
love you, man. Okay?
But you're a bomb magnet.
You got blown up seven times.
Hey, you can come stay with me
until we square your shit up.
We should get a house.
Just us.
Man Love Thursdays every day.
That's supposed to make me feel better?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, fagging out with your cocoa ass?
- Oh, my "cocoa ass," huh?
ADAM: Shots fired.
Whoo!
Do you ever think about Emory?
Emory's alive, man. He's, uh...
he's back home in Arkansas.
Maybe we should go visit him.
Yeah, you should drive down there.
Do you ever think about Doster?
Let it go.
They teach us that in Basic.
All right.
- # What is love? Baby, #
- Oh, shit!
- # don't hurt me #
- [LAUGHING] Oh...
- this is it!
- # Don't hurt me no more #
- Yeah, Will. It's your song, boy.
- # Baby, don't hurt me, don't hurt me #
# No more #
##
[BOTH GRUNTING, BARKING]
[GRUNTING AND BARKING RAPIDLY]
# What is love? #
[ALL YELLING]
# Yeah, yeah #
##
[ALL GRUNTING TO BEAT]
[SINGING ALONG] # Ooh, ooh #
# I don't know #
# You're not there #
# I give you my love, but you don't care #
# So what is right? #
# What is wrong? #
# Give me a sign #
# What is love? #
- [LAUGHING] What the...?
- Shh.
- [DOOR SLAMS]
- Oh, no.
[LAUGHING] Oh, shit.
[QUIETLY] Hey, man.
- I got kids, man.
- [LAUGHING]
- Sorry, man.
- All right, get your ass on the couch.
Hey, I'm not... I'm not staying here, bro.
- What?
- It's a fucking dump, man.
What do you mean, man? My house is beautiful.
Come on. There you go. That's all you.
- Oh, this is me?
- That's you right there.
- Get...
- [GRUNTS] Fuck you.
- [LAUGHING]
- Such an asshole, man.
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
Hey, man, seriously, I'm about to kick your ass.
Hey, take your shoes off.
- They're muddy as shit.
- Sorry, bro.
You're not gonna come snuggle, Shoe?
Nah, you're not my type.
- I don't like redheaded, ugly-looking dudes.
- [BOTH LAUGHING]
Here you go, princess.
All right, you cool, man?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Hey, this couch is yours for
as long as you need it.
All right?
Yeah.
You're a good man, Sergeant. You know that.
All right.
See you tomorrow, man.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
##
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- Will.
- Why are you doing this?
- Don't.
- Don't what?
Please don't. Not here.
- What?
- It's over. I am sorry, but it's over.
We were gonna get married.
Cleaned me out.
- Took my daughter.
- She is my daughter, not yours.
How can you say that?
- Now, I... I've been there since she was born.
- You were gone forever.
That was 'cause of us.
- I enlisted for us.
- I... I can't do this with you.
Do... do what?
- Do what? I...
- Don't make me call security.
You've got to go.
Where do I go?
[SNIFFS]
##
Told him to stay.
Why wouldn't he just stay on the fucking couch?
- Fuck.
- He got blown up seven times.
He was fucked up.
- Normal people don't get blown up.
- Normal people don't get robbed blind
- by their fucking fiancée, man.
- They don't get blown up, bro.
If he was so fucked up, why
didn't he say anything?
Army won't let me redeploy. They're
trying to discharge me.
For what?
What do you think?
My shit's scrambled.
I don't belong here.
##
WOMAN: My boy...
was hurt.
He was injured.
You couldn't see it, but, uh... but he was.
I could hear it in his voice.
In the way he talked to me on the phone.
But there was only so much he would let me do.
If you're hurt like he was...
talk to someone.
Please don't do this.
Fire party, atten-hut!
Port arms.
Fire party, prepare for three volleys.
Half-right face.
Ten-hut.
Ready. Aim.
Adam Schumann?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry. I was gonna come
and introduce myself earlier.
WILL'S MOM: I just wanted to say thank you
- for looking after my son over there.
- He was my brother.
We looked after each other.
He'd been struggling for months over there.
We planned ahead. We found a
treatment facility in California.
The guy who runs this place,
uh, he was a soldier.
He's been doing it for 30 years.
So, if you know anybody who needs...
ADAM: Thank you.
I'm really glad you're here.
##
When did she become friends with Doster's wife?
When he took over our platoon.
Well, does she know that he
took your place on the rig?
No.
Let's go, bro.
Can we go?
Thought you were on Klonopin.
It... doesn't work.
None of it works.
ADAM: Will liked to hunt,
so we're going hunting.
- Be careful.
- I'm Captain Careful.
[DOOR OPENS]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- Let's go shoot something.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
Nobody knows you fought unless you
got your fucking arm blown off.
I'd take it.
I'd rather be a hero with my
ass blown off than this shit.
Don't even feel like me anymore.
Guess you don't know what I mean.
You don't got stress.
You're good, right?
I don't think that guy lost his
arm picking flowers, man.
What the fuck does that mean?
Means we don't know shit about him.
Would you rather lose your leg than this?
- What, below the knee?
- Nah, above the knee.
Fuck it... I'll take it.
- How about your ear?
- Well, can I still hear?
Nope.
But you can still finger-fuck it.
And you can hear out of your other ear.
[CHUCKLING]
But I won't look like no war hero.
Just... just some freak with no ear.
Hey, what was that... you remember
that Bravo got his lips blown off?
Who? Pussy Face?
- Yeah, Pussy Face.
- [CHUCKLING] Oh, fuck.
- That's what you want?
- Hell no.
You remember what you said
to me the day Doster died?
When we were dragging him inside?
I remember his skin was
so burnt, it was falling off.
The smell.
- You don't remember what you said?
- No, bro. I don't remember shit.
My memory's shot. What did I say?
You said that none of it would have
happened if I'd have been there.
That's a fucked thing to say, man.
[RUMMAGING]
All right. I'm gonna scare
'em towards the water.
You push up from that bend.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[FOOTSTEPS SLOSHING]
[BEEP, WHIRRING]
[SIGHS, SNIFFS]
##
[BRANCH SNAPS]
[LOW GROWLING]
##
[BEEP, WHIRRING]
Solo!
Hey.
[BRANCHES SNAP]
[PANTING]
[GASPS]
Hey. You trying to get fucking shot?
- What?
- What the fuck are you doing out there?
I wasn't out there.
- Yeah, you were. I saw you out there.
- I didn't even make it out there.
It's too dark. I forgot my goggles.
- I saw you.
- No, you didn't. It wasn't me.
SOLO: You all right?
No, man, I'm not all right.
Fuck.
I still... taste his blood.
I carried him down those stairs.
I can still taste his blood.
What do we do?
[SNIFFS]
We get some help.
Yeah.
Okay.
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- SASKIA: Are you coming to bed?
- Yeah.
Think I'm gonna try and find
a job early tomorrow.
[SASKIA SIGHS]
Okay.
You all right?
ADAM: I'm good.
You got mud everywhere, so...
Clean up. Come to bed.
##
[QUIET CHATTER]
Alea's pregnant.
Yeah? Nice, man. That's great.
Hell yeah.
You're gonna do great. Seriously.
Kids change everything.
I'm gonna name him after me
so I don't forget his name.
Can I have your VA card, sir?
- My VA card?
- Mm-hmm.
What, am I supposed to have one of those?
Well, if you don't have one, you
need to go to the second floor.
Okay? You understand?
Special Forces guy was telling
me Ecstasy cures all this shit.
Yeah?
What the hell are we doing here?
[SOLO CHUCKLES]
Sergeant Schumann.
Yes, sir.
At ease.
I didn't recognize you in civvies.
I don't recognize myself sometimes, either, sir.
Got out a few months back.
Why'd you go and do that?
The wife. I was downrange
three times with two kids.
Roger that.
What's this line you're in?
We're applying for a service connection, sir.
Shoe, you were my hammer out there.
Don't let these young guys
see you fold like this.
It's bad for morale.
Bad for Big Army.
[PATS ARM]
##
ADAM: That shiny-medal motherfucker.
He didn't do our war.
He wasn't fucking kicking in doors.
He fought his war at a fucking computer.
Anybody home?
Fuck 'em.
- [JAXSON CRYING]
- ADAM: Eggs, no chocolate chips.
ZOE: Come on, Jaxy. Just sing it.
SASKIA: Hurry up, Zo. We got to get to school.
Will's mom gave me the number to
this treatment facility out West.
Out West?
California.
Fuck.
This shit could give me PTSD.
MAN: This is our care package. Fill it out,
and on review, you will be directed to a
primary care physician and psychiatrist.
- How long does that take?
- Usually 12 weeks, but we're in arrears, so...
- Arrears?
- Yeah, we're backed up.
It could be six to nine months.
Are you kidding?
[CHUCKLES]
- You think these guys can wait that long?
- Excuse me?
I said, how many of these guys
in this room do you think
- will make it six to nine months?
- All right...
- If you're finished...
- No, I'm not finished, man.
Look... we need to see somebody, okay?
You're feeding me this
fucking "arrears" bullshit.
My boy here fought his ass off.
- Yeah.
- All right? He did his job.
- Now do yours.
- I'll see him.
Okay? I... I've got 20 minutes left on my lunch.
Just have him come around the side.
Okay. Thank you.
- All right, look alive.
- You're up.
What about you?
Nah, you go first. I'll get the next one.
WOMAN: It says here you're
having trouble remembering.
Can you tell me the date?
It's... it's May.
Good. How about day and date?
Um...
Thursday.
Today is Wednesday, May 7.
[CHUCKLES]
Are you having any suicidal ideation?
I... I just want to get back to my unit.
It must be hard to be separated
from your brothers like that.
Yeah.
We're having a baby.
That's great. So you'll have a new unit.
Do you remember the date?
Um... yeah, you said, uh... Thursday, May.
So we're having a little trouble with
that. Let's try word association.
To me, the word "Wednesday"
sounds like "wedding day."
I always wanted a big wedding.
Did you have a wedding?
Yes, ma'am.
So, when I ask you what day it is, I
want you to think of your wedding.
[SIGHS] Are you still having nightmares?
Sometimes I see Doster. He's on fire.
But mostly I'm awake.
You see him when you're awake?
And the smell.
Do you remember what day it is?
Wednesday, wedding day.
Good job.
You see, that's great.
And we can use that to remember anything.
So you could help me fill this out?
[SIGHING] Oh, God.
I'm sorry. I'm... I'm booked with patients
during my lunch all week.
- Can your wife help us?
- I... I haven't told her.
You got to share this with her.
##
[SETS PAPERS ASIDE]
[SNIFFS, SIGHS]
ALEA: "Have you used drugs other than
those required for medical reasons?"
Never. [CHUCKLES]
"Are you always able to stop
using drugs when you want?"
Mostly.
They're drugs. It's a stupid question.
"Have drugs ever created a problem
between you and your spouse?"
- No.
- You were arrested for possession four times.
That wasn't a problem?
Well, we weren't married.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay, the next section is
"exposure to combat scale."
"Were you ever under enemy fire?"
I feel like I am right now.
Hey. Baby, you're doing good.
"Were you ever pinned down?"
No.
"How often did you fire rounds at the enemy?"
- Uh, I'm supposed to count?
- Options are: "never,"
"one to two times," "three to 12 times,"
"13 to 50 times," "over 50."
- Over 50.
- [LOUD METALLIC SCRAPING]
"How often did you see someone get hit
by incoming or outgoing rounds?"
[VOICE ECHOING] "Never," "one to two
times," "three to 12 times," "13 to 50,"
"over 50."
##
[SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
ALEA: Solo.
Hey.
[ADAM AND ZOE TALKING INDISTINCTLY IN DISTANCE]
##
[MUFFLED CHATTER]
[MUFFLED CHATTER CONTINUES]
- ADAM: Oh, it's nice in here.
- ZOE: I know.
["SWEET LULLABY" BY T
BONE BURNETT PLAYING]
Damn.
Look at you.
Where'd that come from?
Don't worry about it.
# In blood we sit in dark, we die #
# Don't blink now, sweet lullaby... #
[DISTORTED BANGING AND CREAKING]
[BATTLE GUNFIRE]
[DISTANT GUNSHOT, WHIZZING BULLET]
[LOUD BANG]
Get off! [PANTING]
SASKIA: What happened?
What'd I do?
I don't understand. Tell me what to do.
I need you to talk to me, Adam.
It's time. I've given you months.
I thought we were broke. You're
buying fucking lingerie.
I thought you were fine.
You're lying to me. I found
your VA questionnaire.
- Everything's a lie.
- I'm not lying.
You're fucked up.
You're not looking for a job.
You're sick, and I can't do anything if
you don't fucking talk to me, Adam.
I have to be sick, or I can't get my benefits.
So, you don't want to die?
It was multiple choice, and
you said you wanted to die.
Was that a lie?
Hmm?
Adam.
I don't know.
I want to go to the VA with you next time.
All right.
Adam talked about a treatment
place in California.
- Could I go there?
- Look, the problem is,
is the Army doesn't have
record of you participating
in this incident that caused your TBI, and
so I can't get you service-connected.
- What, there's no record?
- You didn't report an injury
at the time of the incident.
- Doster was dead. I dragged him out.
- They're denying benefits
until we prove that you were in the Humvee.
We need to go back to your COs
and get written testimony.
- What, they didn't believe I was there?
- We just need to go back and get proof.
MAN: Come on, Specialist. Sit down.
Do you know why this is the greatest country...
on the planet? Well, I'll tell you. It's
because, with a click of a finger,
I can order 20 pounds of beef and have
it delivered to my door in 24 hours.
The terrorists cannot do that, and
that is why they will never win.
[SIGHING] So...
- sounds like you got some bad paper.
- Yes, sir.
I'm glad that you're seeking treatment,
because we got 22 veterans a day killing
themselves. And I don't get it.
Warriors get stressed.
We know this.
But this obsession to end your own life?
I can't wrap my head around it.
We don't want you to be a
statistic, though, do we?
No, sir.
You signed up during wartime.
You got yourself a war.
But they don't believe that I was there, sir.
They're as wrong as two boys fucking in church.
Give me that file. Let me see what you got.
[SIGHS]
I just need a statement saying that I was
driving the rig when Doster was hit, sir.
- American Samoa? Where is that?
- South Pacific, sir.
- It's a territory.
- So, does that make you a...
a citizen or...?
How's that work?
I was able to apply for citizenship
after basic training, sir.
I'm going for the New Yorks. [SIGHS]
Fuck it, you know?
Yeah. Boom, boom, boom.
Why are you braking? Why?!
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[TIRES SQUEAK]
You'd have done great in Iraq, babe.
We never slowed down. We just ran 'em over.
Did you drive?
I rode shotgun and looked for the IEDs.
They'd hide 'em in trash like that, or...
once they got smarter, they just
started cementing 'em in curbs.
So, when you see trash on the road here...?
I look.
That's the first real thing you've
told me about the war.
- I feel so much better now.
- SASKIA: Hey, don't be an asshole.
Two Army Commendation Medals.
An Army Achievement Medal.
Impressive.
You never told me about those.
Is there a specific incident that troubles you?
Maybe a name?
Emory.
What happened with Emory?
I dropped him.
I was carrying him.
I dropped him. And they had to
cut two inches of his brain out.
And then Doster happened.
What happened to Doster?
Why don't you tell us our options?
There is no cure for trauma,
but we can learn to manage it.
Long-term care has the best results,
but every facility is different.
Some are four weeks. Some are nine months.
What works for one person
may not work for another.
But all these places are equally
difficult to get into,
so the smartest thing to do would
be to apply everywhere
and cross our fingers.
Cross our fingers?
There are hundreds of thousands
of men and women seeking help.
SASKIA: But he's a veteran.
That's what I mean.
There are hundreds of thousands
of veterans seeking help.
Will we get priority to places closest to us?
I'm afraid not.
- What do we do in the meantime?
- What if I had a job?
- I think a job would help.
- A job is good.
Your benefits won't be kicking in for
another couple of months, so...
Another couple months?
Wow. I mean, what the fuck
is going on around here?
- [PAPERS RUSTLING]
- [SIGHS]
I have a position at a heavy-ordnance range.
Okay, he wants to kill himself,
and you want him to work at a gun range?
It's a tank range.
- You think I could kill myself with a tank?
- Maybe.
- Well, it would take some serious planning.
- Well, you're pretty fucking resourceful.
- [SASKIA CHUCKLES]
- I used to be good at that.
At what?
Making you laugh.
[SNIFFLING]
Was I laughing?
[CHUCKLES, CRIES]
You should have told me
I was married to a hero.
I'm not a hero.
Hero enough.
I just want to get back in our house.
- Me, too. We're not that far off.
- Oh, yeah?
- You win the Powerball and not tell me?
- Amanda loaned us some money.
Amanda Doster?
Yeah.
- We were at Will's funeral, and she offered.
- What the fuck are you doing?
I told her we were trying to
get back into our house.
Do you not fucking get that she has that
money because her husband's dead?
And that her husband is dead because of me?
What the fuck, Saskia?
- Fucking Christ.
- ##
##
[GARAGE DOOR CLANKING AND WHIRRING]
[QUIET CHATTER]
What's up, homey? What you want? I
got nickels, dimes, two finger sacks.
What about some Ecstasy?
Some Ecstasy? Man, I don't
sell that around here.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Come on, man. Roll it up. Who I got to see?
Fuck does that mean? Fuck, is you
12? Show me some bread, dawg.
- I got some pills.
- I don't fucking take pills.
I look like a fucking pawnshop
or something to you, nigga?
Well, you look like your fucking balls ain't
dropped. Huh? How about this, motherfucker?
[INDISTINCT ARGUING]
##
[DOG GROWLS]
[INDISTINCT, EXCITED CHATTER]
[GROWLING, CHATTER CONTINUE]
[BOTTLE POPS OPEN]
What up, Big Army?
You all out of pocket here.
How'd you know I was military?
Yeah, I stormed that desert myself
back in '91. 24th Infantry.
All right.
Did you get in on waivers?
You got that look.
Army saved my life.
What they doing for you now?
Got to make your own way now.
MAN: Ah, yeah!
[MEN EXCLAIMING]
MAN: Oh, shit!
[INDISTINCT, EXCITED CHATTER]
- You know where I can score some Ecstasy?
- Ecstasy?
[CHUCKLING] Man, does this
look like a goddamn rave?
It's not for a rave.
- It's for an injury.
- Shit, if you're injured, man,
doctors up there at Fort Riley giving
out that oxy like it's candy.
It's not that kind of injury.
[DOGS GROWLING, SPECTATORS EXCLAIMING]
You was all in it, wasn't you?
Did you lose some guys?
Or you one of them murdering motherfuckers?
- [VICIOUS GROWLING]
- [BANGING]
[DOG YELPING IN PAIN]
[CROWD QUIETS]
[MURMURING, SCATTERED SHOUTS]
[DOG WHIMPERING]
[WEAK, GRUFF BREATHING]
Hey, buddy. It's okay.
It's all right.
I got you.
It's okay.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- [WHIMPERING]
- I got you.
- ADAM: Was this dog fight downtown?
You're gonna make it. You're
gonna be all right, buddy.
ADAM: Can't be going down there, man.
- You got a kid coming.
- I got you.
Hey, stop moving, man. You're
vibrating the whole damn table.
Do you remember the dogs in Rustamiyah?
- That runt that went on raids?
- Little Caesar.
He was Emory's dog, wasn't he?
You ever talk to him?
No.
Do you think he's like us?
I just told you, man, I haven't
fucking talked to him.
Do you remember what that
Iraqi cop did to Caesar?
Yeah.
Wanted to kill that motherfucker.
Two guys in Bravo got back at him.
- You hear about that?
- No. What'd they do?
Same shit he did to Caesar.
Held him down and snipped his fucking
Achilles with a bolt cutter.
Fuck yeah.
- [UNDER BREATH] Fuck...
- We're gonna be all right, man.
[SOLO SNIFFLING, SHUDDERING]
We're gonna get in a treatment
facility somewhere.
And then what?
Huh? Just...
Just goes away?
What is that?
It's a dog.
I can see that.
- Why is it here and not at a vet?
- It... it's a fighting dog.
They won't let dogs like this in.
[SASKIA SCOFFS]
Were you outside of Amanda's earlier tonight?
Nope.
She said you were.
She saw your truck.
Well, if you weren't sucking money off her,
you probably wouldn't fucking care.
I care about you, not her.
The dog has to go.
It's a pit bull. We have kids.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- [FRUSTRATED GROAN]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING ON FLOOR]
We're not allowed dogs in our apartment.
[ADAM CHUCKLES]
Well, shit.
I guess I got a dog.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER ON VIDEO GAME]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
[HEAVY GUNFIRE ON VIDEO GAME]
[BATTLE SOUND EFFECTS CONTINUE]
[SIZZLING]
Something's burning.
Alea.
[BATTLE SOUND EFFECTS CONTINUE]
[SCREAMS]
Fuck! [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING, YELLING]
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- [GRUNTING, YELLING CONTINUE]
[ALEA SCREAMING]
[WHIMPERING]
Mom, call the police!
[WHISPERING] It's okay.
[TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
- [THUD]
- [JAXSON CRYING]
- Oh, my God, the baby!
- ADAM: I'm so sorry.
SASKIA: Jaxy, come here, baby.
It's okay. Mommy's got you.
What happened?
- Did you drop him?
- I don't know.
- Shh.
- [CRYING CONTINUES]
Get away from us, Adam. It's okay, Jaxy.
Mommy's here.
Mommy's here. I'm right here.
I know. I know.
I'm sorry. Fell asleep.
[CRYING CONTINUES]
It's okay, Jaxson. Mommy's
here. I'm right here. I know.
Shh.
[KEYS JINGLING]
SASKIA: Shh.
Baby.
[CRYING]
You need help.
- You have to go away.
- I'm sorry.
You've got to go.
- [KNOCKING]
- MAN: Police!
I can't help you, Sol.
[KNOCKING]
I can't help you.
##
[SHUDDERING BREATHS]
[TAKES TWO DEEP BREATHS]
##
[GUN DROPS]
[GASPING BREATHS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING, MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING]
What up, Big Army?
You still looking for Molly?
Who?
Ecstasy.
I got your medicine.
Get your ass in the car.
- Are you some kind of island nigga?
- Samoan.
Damn, Samo, you looking raggedy, man.
I got your shit.
But here's what I need from you.
I give you a car and an address.
You park the goods and walk away.
- That's it?
- That's it.
Why don't these guys do it?
'Cause these are my guys.
And you're just some grunt nobody recognizes.
And if shit gets hairy,
oh, you can Rambo your way out of it.
I need shoes.
[LAUGHTER]
Hey, Jay, man, stop by the Big 5.
Let's get this big motherfucker a pair of shoes.
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
SASKIA: Adam?
Is Jax okay?
He's fine.
- Where are you?
- I'm in Arkansas.
Arkansas? Why?
I need to find Emory. Babe, I can't live like this.
Adam...
I'm gonna get this job, and we're
gonna move back into our house.
We can move in right away.
It'll be like we're starting over.
Does that sound good?
That sounds great.
I love you.
Love you, too.
[KNOCKING]
Hey, Emory, it's Shoe.
EMORY: Come on in.
What's up, man?
Where you at?
Right here.
- There's my man.
- [CHUCKLING]
- You got skinny.
- Really? Did I?
Hell yeah. Skinnier than you were.
- You got kind of fat.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
Got fat, did I?
- Yeah.
- Well, fuck.
- You just fucking show up, huh?
- Yeah, what do you want me to do?
- You ain't got no phone.
- Fuck you talking...?
I got a phone right there. I got Internet.
What the fuck you think? You think I'm just
living out here eating fucking squirrels?
Yeah, maybe.
Dude, come on. Give me a hand with this.
- I got to get this shit on.
- Need some help?
Hell yeah. I've been trying to get this
- fucking thing on all morning.
- Yeah, man, let's go.
It is physically impossible
to put that on by yourself.
All right. God, man.
- Just tell me what to do.
- Yeah.
[GRUNTING] Yeah, there it is.
Yeah. Nice and snug.
All right, come on. Get up in there. Put
some fucking muscle in it, Shoe.
- You good? Yeah, more? All right, man.
- [GRUNTING]
- There it is.
- Shit, how do you usually
- get this thing on?
- Fucking roll around on the floor,
wait for my nurse.
Here.
Right over there.
- All right. There?
- Yep.
[GRUNTS] There it is. Now,
pull that around there.
- Come on.
- All right.
All right. Yeah.
- Something like that? Tighten you up.
- Yeah.
- [GRUNTING]
- You're gonna break a rib, man.
Sorry, all right.
Piece of cake.
[EMORY GRUNTING]
[SIGHS, CLEARS THROAT]
So I heard Will shot himself.
Yeah.
He didn't say shit, either, man,
so we had no idea, you know?
[SIGHS]
So you come down here to save me?
No, man. Came down to see you.
See how my boy's doing.
[EMORY WHOOPING]
EMORY: Yeah, boy! Yeah, boy! Yeah!
- [LAUGHING]
- You know, you drive like my wife, man.
Watch this. [GRUNTS, LAUGHS]
I scared mine off.
- [LAUGHING] Yeah? I bet.
- Yeah.
One night, I woke up, I had
my hands around her neck.
I said I was gonna kill her,
dude. I swear to God.
- She didn't like that?
- Fuck no, she didn't like that, dude.
They don't like that.
- It's good to see you, dude.
- Good to see you, too, man.
This is how I get my tits off, dude.
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- EMORY: Get 'em off, dude.
[EMORY WHOOPING]
I fucking love it, dude.
Hey, let me ask you... what's
with all this trash?
Oh, you still looking for the bomb, huh?
Why didn't you look me up sooner, dude?
I should have.
I dropped my kid last night.
My baby boy, man... I... was
supposed to hold him.
Saskia gave him to me. I
fell asleep like a shitbag.
Fell right off.
So, you know, I dropped him,
started thinking about you.
He's gonna be all right, you know,
but... I dropped you, and...
What, and I'm not all right? Hmm?
Why don't you help me piss?
[GRUNTING]
That fall took out my left side.
Know that, dude?
Wasn't the sniper round they
took out of my head or...
that two inches they cut out of my brain.
It was you fucking dropping me.
Is that what you think, dude?
[LAUGHING] That the shit you told yourself?
- You didn't drop me off a fucking building dude.
- Well, you were alive, and then you weren't.
I'm alive now, motherfucker.
[GRUNTING]
- Hey, you need another one, buddy?
- Hell yeah, I need another one. Fuck you think?
- You don't think I need another one?
- I got you.
All right.
They're fucked up, dude.
Hey, you see where the shot came from?
Someone did.
Solo? Solo did.
- Yeah, you couldn't get the bastards?
- No, I was carrying you down, man.
You were.
Fuck, I should have went after him.
Me and you were the tallest
ones on that rooftop, dude.
- They go for the tall ones.
- Yep.
You know, I think about
that. What if I was short?
I wonder if I'd still be like this.
- I think about that, dude.
- Yeah, but you'd be short.
You'd have to live the rest of your life
as a short guy, man. [CHUCKLES]
Dude, I'm tall as fuck, dude.
I can't stand up on my
own, but I'm tall as fuck.
- [BOTH LAUGHING]
- The girls, they love that.
Yeah?
You saved my life.
I dropped you.
I'm alive because of you.
I know this don't look like much of a life,
but every morning I get up, I'm grateful.
I'm grateful I'm alive.
["MUTRON ANGEL" BY OUTKAST
FEATURING WHILD PEACH PLAYS]
# Ooh... #
# Ooh, ooh #
- # In the eye of the storm #
- [DOOR OPENS]
# Looking out through the rain #
There he is.
# Gabriel, blow your horn... #
Rolling.
How you feel?
- Good. I feel good.
- Yeah.
Man, I came back to the same
shit. No job, no help, nothing.
We're out there fighting their wars for
shit that we ain't even got over here.
But we're fighters.
We make do.
- Yeah.
# Powerful, magnificent and so divine #
# Soldiers stay affronted,
it'll blow your mind... #
You ready to go again?
You straight?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- You better be.
'Cause this is real right here.
You don't be fucking this up.
These boys are waiting. You got an hour.
[RINGTONE PLAYING]
- Hello.
- MAN: Hi, Adam.
This is Fred Gusman from
Pathway Home in California.
I've got your DD 214 here.
In your message, you said you're looking
to get into a facility as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
Good. Well, then let's get you out here.
We can get you on a bus tomorrow.
You ready to commit to this?
##
- [TIRES SQUEAL]
- [MAN GRUNTS]
Fuck.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Hello?
WOMAN: Is this Tausolo Aieti?
- Who is this?
- I'm a nurse calling from Geary Community.
Your wife is in labor.
She arrived by ambulance, and
there are some complications,
- so we're having to rush her into surgery.
- The baby, the... is the baby okay?
She just asked you to get here right away, sir.
Where?
- That's Geary Community Hospital.
- Where is it?
We're just off Horne Street.
Horne Street. H... H... Horne Street.
Like a... like a car horn?
That's right, sir.
Alea Aieti.
[SHUDDERING BREATH]
You all right?
Come meet your boy.
- I... I thought you were...
- It's okay.
Come here.
##
Wellcome little Solo.
I am so pleased to meet you.
[BABY COOING]
Talofa, little man.
Did you tell Emory you dropped him?
Yeah.
Is he like us?
He's tough as hell, man.
Wish you could've seen him.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
I got a bed at that treatment center in California.
- So you're leaving.
- Yeah.
Leave tonight.
They're gonna ask you about Doster.
You gonna tell them how fucked
it was you weren't there?
Do you want to know fucked?
The Humvee was burning.
And I got all the guys out.
We were huddled in a ditch.
But I forgot Doster.
I forgot he was with us.
Only for a second, but by the time I got back...
...it was too late.
How come you never told me that?
'Cause you never asked.
None of this would have happened
if you were there.
You would have seen the bomb.
You don't forget.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
ADAM: Why aren't you answering that?
Look how perfect he is.
Can't name him after me.
He's too perfect.
##
[KEYS JINGLING]
[LOCK CLICKS]
DANTE: You fucked up, Samo.
You think we don't know where you're at?
There's a liquor store on Pinkerton.
Park behind the liquor store and leave the keys.
- I'm gonna drop this, then we're done.
- You cost me 30 grand, Samo.
Hell yeah, we're done.
Liquor store on Pinkerton.
Pink, liquor, pink, liquor, pink...
I love you, Zo.
Daddy's gonna be home soon, all right?
What if she gets scared?
Who?
Your doll? [CHUCKLES]
You just tell her that everything's
gonna be all right.
That doesn't work, Dad.
Well... this time, it will.
[LINE RINGING]
ADAM: Hey, man. Everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm all right, bro. I just, uh...
just got into some shit.
ADAM: What kind of shit?
SOLO: Uh, some guys. I got something
that belongs to them.
If I get out of this, Shoe, I should
probably leave here a while.
Where you at?
SOLO: I'm under that bridge.
ADAM: Wait there for me, okay?
I'm on my way.
Okay, Zo, I need you to be
good for Mommy, okay?
ZOE: Okay, Daddy.
Is everything all right?
I love you.
I'll call you from the bus.
SOLO: Pink, liquor, pink, liquor.
Park behind pink liquor.
##
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[BUZZING]
Come on, answer your fucking phone.
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[GUNFIRE, GLASS BREAKING]
[CAR ALARM WHOOPING]
[PANTING]
[TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
[TRAIN SCREECHING NEARBY]
DANTE: Get the fuck out and check.
[TRAIN HORN BLARING]
Fuck.
[TRAIN SCREECHING NEARBY]
[SIREN BLARING]
DANTE: Fuck! Cops coming!
Fall back! Let's go!
[VEHICLE DOORS CLOSE]
[VEHICLE DRIVES AWAY]
[SIRENS CONTINUE BLARING]
[SIRENS FADE INTO DISTANCE]
[PANTING]
- Hey, what the fuck's going on?
- I fucked up.
What do you mean? Are you hurt?
Are you all right?
I... I don't know what I'm doing,
Shoe. I'm... I'm... I'm fucked.
[PANTING]
All right, I'm getting you out of here.
ADAM: You're gonna take my
place at the treatment facility.
- We're swapping spots. That's all this is.
- And what about you?
Don't worry about me. First bed opens
up, I'm gonna get out there.
- But my wife and my boy, bro.
- I got 'em.
- You trust me? I'm gonna take care of 'em.
- I can't leave you.
You're getting on this bus.
Maybe you're just too afraid to go.
- Maybe.
- Can't leave you behind, Shoe.
We're not downrange, man. It's not how it
works. All right? You take what comes.
So I go and get better while
you sit here, broken.
I'll figure it out.
- Don't worry about me.
- Yeah...
Get your ass in this bus.
[SIGHING] Ah...
[HANDS SLAP]
We had some bad days, bro.
Maybe that's all they were. Just bad days.
We had some good days, too.
[BOTH CHUCKLE QUIETLY]
##
ADAM: Hey, Fred, it's Adam.
I, uh... sent somebody in my place.
Can you give him my bed?
FRED: Uh... okay.
Well, we'll get him squared away,
but where's that leave you?
I don't know what you mean.
Well, you were finally gonna get
some help, and you gave it away.
How does that feel?
I, uh... I feel alone, man. Yeah,
they're gone, you know?
Everyone's gone; I'm still here.
Look, talking about this isn't gonna cure you,
but it can buy you some relief.
You got to open this up.
You got to share it.
[BIRDS CHIRPING AND SQUAWKING]
[CHILDREN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Don't come out too far, 'cause it's chilly, okay?
Adam?
Everything okay?
[SIGHS]
##
ADAM: I don't know how much James
talked about the guys in our platoon,
but I can't tell you how your husband
died unless I tell you about Emory.
[INDISTINCT RADIO COMMUNICATION]
##
Stop the truck.
What you got?
MAN: [OVER RADIO] Hey, 1-1,
what's the holdup up there?
- I don't see nothing, man.
- Shoe don't see it. He feels it.
This is 1-1. Alternate route.
We're gonna hang a left here on Dead Girl Road.
- [OVER RADIO] Copy that.
- Who named that street?
We did.
You don't remember her?
All right, let's go.
[PERSON WHISTLING LOUDLY]
[WINGS FLUTTERING]
[PROJECTILE WHIZZING]
[LOUD BANG]
RPG! Everybody get out!
Let's go! Engine's down!
All right, Building 20, rooftop! Move!
Fuck!
[OVER RADIO] Anybody have eyes on it?
Where did that come from?
Where'd it come from?
##
[SHOUTING, GUNFIRE IN DISTANCE]
EMORY: Stairway to Heaven.
- EMORY: Go, go. Move, move.
- SOLO: Stick with me.
EMORY: Where'd they go?
ADAM: [UNDER BREATH] Fuck.
[OVER RADIO] What's your
status, 1-1? I need a status.
We got a hajji fire escape.
- Where the hell?
- [OVER RADIO] A rep, 1-1. Now.
This is 1-1. We are clear on Building
20. Building 20 is green.
[OVER RADIO] Roger. Set security
and take overwatch.
QRF's still five minutes out.
This is some fucking Charlie
Foxtrot bullshit, man.
- Oh, I gotta get juicy.
- That's why you don't eat Indian food in...
- [GUNSHOT ECHOING]
- Man down!
Hang on, Emory. I got you.
Fuck!
ADAM: I put us on that roof.
- Those were my orders.
- I got you, bud.
He took a bullet for it.
[GRUNTING]
Then I dropped him.
I choked on his blood.
[PANTING, WHEEZING]
I fucking dropped him.
[COUGHS, GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
##
- I can't stop looking at it.
- # That is just so typically me #
# Oh, baby, baby #
# Oops, I did it again #
# I played with your heart #
# Got lost in the game #
# Oh, baby, baby, oops... #
How you boys holding up?
Any update on Emory?
Emory has a tough road ahead.
But, uh, I think there's a real good chance
they get him home with a heartbeat.
Then what happens?
Give us a minute, Solo.
- MAN: Happy birthday, dude!
- [LAUGHTER]
[LAUGHTER, EXCITED CHATTER]
DOSTER: Hey!
Knock it off.
- Listen, as leaders, we make decisions.
- I made the wrong call.
You changed the route.
It was another engagement.
You have to trust your instincts.
My instincts were wrong.
Listen, I'm signed up for a video linkup
tomorrow morning with my wife,
but I want you to take my call, and
I'm gonna take your place on patrol.
- Can't let you do that.
- Sure, you can.
- Nah, those are my guys. I should be out there.
- Take the day off.
- Sergeant, that's my patrol.
- Schumann.
You're sitting this one out.
[AIRCRAFT BUZZING OVERHEAD]
[VEHICLE HORNS HONKING]
[HORNS CONTINUE HONKING]
MAN: Medic! Medic!
- What happened? What happened?
- Medic! Medic!
- Medic! We got hit!
- Who is it?
- It's Doster.
- He was in your seat.
- Medic!
Fuck! Get him! Get him! Get him! Let's go!
- Go, go!
- Where were you, man?
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
SOLO: None of this would have
happened if you were there, Shoe.
None of this would have happened
if you were there.
[SOLO PANTING]
- MAN: Private Waller.
- Here, First Sergeant.
- Sergeant White.
Specialist Aieti.
- Here, First Sergeant.
- Sergeant Schumann.
- Sergeant Doster.
Sergeant James Doster.
Sergeant First Class James D. Doster.
Present arms.
[BUGLE PLAYING "TAPS"]
[SIGHS]
God, Adam.
Amanda, he took my seat.
- That was supposed to be me.
- But it wasn't you.
You're still here.
James wouldn't want this for you.
He would want you to live.
You live.
That's how you honor him.
##
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[JAXSON YOWLING]
- Jaxy, sing it.
- Zoe?
##
I'm home.
ZOE: Daddy's home!
ADAM: Hey, sweetheart.
##
# Some say freedom is free
but I tend to disagree #
# I say freedom is won, through
the barrel of a gun #
# Had a brother in Iraq
He didn't come back #
# I asked, "Why, oh, why
do soldiers gotta die?" #
# Some say freedom is free
but I tend to disagree #
# I say freedom is won, through
the blood of someone's son #
# Some say freedom is free
but I tend to disagree #
# I say freedom is won, through
the barrel of a gun #
# Daddy died in Vietnam, he
was killed at Khe Sanh #
# I asked, "Why, oh, why
do soldiers gotta die?" #
# Some say freedom is free
but I tend to disagree #
# I say freedom is won, through
the blood of someone's son #
# Some say freedom is free
but I tend to disagree #
# I say freedom is won, through
the barrel of a gun #
# Had a brother in Iraq
He didn't come back #
# I asked, "Why, oh, why
do soldiers gotta die?" #
# Mm-mm-mm, mm-mm-mm #
# Mm-mm-mm-mm, mm-mm-mm #
# Mm-mm-mm-mm, mm-mm-mm. #
##
[SONG ENDS]